name: 'Present Simple: He, She, It'
questions:
  -
    question: 'He $ magazines.'
    answers:
      - read
      - 'does read'
      - reads
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'My mom $ TV.'
    answers:
      - 'don''t watch'
      - 'doesn''t watch'
      - 'don''t watches'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'They $ near here.'
    answers:
      - 'doesn''t live'
      - 'don''t live'
      - 'don''t lives'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: 'Tom $ two brothers.'
    answers:
      - have
      - haves
      - has
    correct: 3
  -
    question: '$ tea or coffe?'
    answers:
      - 'Does she want'
      - 'Does she wants'
      - 'Do she wants'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'What $ for breakfast?'
    answers:
      - 'they have'
      - 'does they have'
      - 'do they have'
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'My sister $ big cars.'
    answers:
      - 'doesn''t likes'
      - 'doesn''t like'
      - 'don''t like'
    correct: 2
  -
    question: '$ cats?'
    answers:
      - 'Do you like'
      - 'Does you like'
      - 'Like you'
    correct: 1
  -
    question: 'She $ to the BBC Radio 1.'
    answers:
      - listen
      - 'does listen'
      - listens
    correct: 3
  -
    question: 'I $ fish.'
    answers:
      - 'not eat'
      - 'don''t eat'
      - 'doesn''t eat'
    correct: 2
